# REBECA SERVAIS

A highly motivated and adaptable professional with over 5 years of experience in customer service and a background in patisserie and big interest in web development. Known for delivering excellent customer care, I bring a strong work ethic, problem-solving abilities, and a commitment to continuous learning.

I am experienced in managing a small jewelry business, including packing orders and stock control, also a basic understanding of HTML, CSS (Flexbox, Grid), and experience using graphic design apps like Procreate, along with a full driving license and my own car.

## CONTACT

- +44 7878273020
- rebecass2207@gmail.com
- RG73TT, Reading.
- github.com/rebecass22

# **EDUCATION**

Web Development Course (HTML, CSS, JavaScript) - Udemy

July 2024 - Present

Level 2 Patisserie and Confectionery Certificate.

Reading College
Sept 2022 - June 2023

Bachillerato/A-Levels in Natural Sciences.

Malaga, Spain. Sept 2016 - May 2018

# VOLUNTEERING

Animal Shelter Volunteer - P.A.D Animal Shelter.

Malaga, Spain. February 2013 to June 2015

Provided care for dogs and cats, maintaining cleanliness and ensuring they were well-fed and helped their social and physical well-being through walks, play, and basic training.

# LANGUAGES

Spanish (Fluent)
English (Fluent)
French (Intermediate)
Italian (Beginner)

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

BARISTA/ALL ROUNDER

#### Coco di Mama

January 2023 to January 2024

- Improved customer satisfaction by consistently providing fast, friendly service and maintaining a clean and welcoming environment. Provide excellent customer service to clients
- Provide excellent customer service to clients
- Complying with health and safety regulations.

BARISTA/APPRENTICE SUPERVISOR

### Starbucks UK

August 2021 to April 2022

- Successfully managed customer interactions, ensuring a seamless experience through detailed attention to preferences and allergies.
- Took on supervisory responsibilities, helping to guide a team in a fast-paced environment.

CABIN CREW MEMBER

# Ryanair Germany and Ryanair UK

October 2018 to May 2019

- Started in Germany, providing exceptional customer service, handling high-pressure situations with professionalism and efficiency.
- Actively contributed to the safety and comfort of passengers during flights, demonstrating excellent teamwork.
- Simulated training required us to practice crisis situations, like cabin decompression and emergency landings. Whilst these were not real events, the level of realism was high, and I learnt how to cope in security and emergency situations without losing focus or effectiveness.
- I gained my airhostess accreditation after successfully passing the training course at the first-time, and was considered worthy of being transferred to Ryanair's busiest area of operation: the United Kingdom.